export const myths = {
  results: [
    {
      correct_answer: 'False',
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      question:
        'Can Covid-19 be transmitted through goods produced in countries where there is ongoing transmission?',
      fact:
        'Although it can last on surfaces for many hours, but the environment, transportation and temperatures during shipment make it difficult for the virus to remain active. If you feel the surface may be contaminated,clean it with a disinfectant and wash your hands after touching it.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question: 'Can Covid-19 be transmitted through mosquitoes?',
      fact:
        'There is no evidence that the novel coronavirus can be transmitted through mosquitoes. The virus can spread through droplets from coughing, sneezing or a patient’s saliva',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question: 'Can drinking alcohol help prevent Covid-19?',
      fact:
        'Drinking alcohol, such as beer, liquor, wine doesn’t help prevent coronavirus. You should wash your hands often, wear masks, and avoid being close to those with a fever and cough.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'True',
      question:
        'Digital thermometers cannot be 100% effective in detecting Covid-19 patients.',
      fact:
        'It may take the virus 1-14 days to incubate and cause symptoms like a fever, so it cannot be used to identify asymptomatic patients.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question:
        'Can UV bulbs used for disinfecting be used to kill Covid-19 on our body?',
      fact:
        'Don’t use UV bulbs on your hands or any part of the body because UV light can irritate your skin.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question:
        'Can Covid-19 be transmitted through goods produced in countries where there is ongoing transmission?',
      fact: '',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question:
        'Can spraying alcohol or chlorine on your body kill the virus inside?',
      fact:
        'Besides not being able to kill the virus inside your body, it could damage clothes and other tissues like eyes and lips.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question: 'Can eating garlic prevent covid-19?',
      fact:
        'Though garlic has some anti-microbial properties, there is no evidence that it can prevent Covid-19.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question:
        'Can rinsing your nose regularly with saline solution prevent Covid-19?',
      fact:
        'Evidence has indicated that rinsing your nose with saline solution can help us recover faster from the common cold, but cannot prevent infectious respiratory diseases or Covid-19.',
    },
    {
      answers: ['True', 'False'],
      correct_answer: 'False',
      question: 'Is there any drug that can prevent and treat Covid-19?',
      fact:
        'At present, there is no drug that can prevent and treat the disease. Patients should receive proper and supportive care to alleviate the symptoms. WHO is accelerating research with all the partners to actively study the treatment for the disease.',
    },
  ],
};
